letsshop.in 2011-11-10

# Privacy Policy

**Our Customers Privacy Is Very Important To Us!** We WILL NOT share ANY customer information or database with ANY other company. We do not believe in or practice spamming. Your order with www.letsshop.in is secure, which means that your personal information and credit card number are encrypted with Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) security. Since credit-card and personal information is only entered on the Order Form, only the Order Forms and Shopping Basket are secure. The secured pages will show a secured URL ("https ://") and a lock sign on your browser. When you enter your credit card number into the Order Form, it is transmitted across the Internet in an encrypted (scrambled) form, then decoded when it gets to the server. Additionally, your credit card information is not transmitted via e-mail (which is not encrypted). Our online credit-card processing software does not allow more than one charge to the same credit card number or for the same order number. Should you have any problem with your credit card charge, we will give you our prompt attention and work to resolve the issue. We want our customers and visitors to feel 100% safe and 100% private when surfing our web site.

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you place an order. Any data we request that is not required will be specified as voluntary or optional. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * To process transactions

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer. 

  * To send periodic emails

The Contact Information / email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information & updates pertaining to your order or request and for Newsletters & Offers.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change.

This policy was last modified on **09th September, 2010.**
